人人影視
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯： 暴龍蛋    圈圈    阿髻    Kiko
翻譯： MythCreator    莉莉絲    胖兔純
時間軸： 濃子   萌    校對： 胖兔純
后期： 孤帆    總監： 米小勒   胖兔純
9月21日
1685年
塞勒姆
我  艾薩克·沃爾頓
I, Isaac Walton...
犯有窺探艾比蓋爾·庫克胴體
Have gazed upon the nakedness of Abigail Cook...
并親吻她之罪
...and did kiss her.
還有呢
And?
還有手淫之罪吧
And -- and did commit the sin of self-pollution.
還有手淫之罪
And committed the sin of self-pollution.
用力給他十鞭
10 hard ones.
就在今天
On this glorious day,
我們的勇士集結于此
Our brave boys muster
共同對抗惡魔的先遣部隊
to face the devil's shock troops...
那些聚集在我們家門口的
French and Indian savages
兇殘法國人及印第安野蠻人
massing in the woods right outside our doors.
而你們要保衛的是什么呢
And what are you going off to defend?
不是所多瑪  而是塞勒姆
Not Sodom, but Salem.
所多瑪是因其罪惡被上帝所滅的城鎮
如果我們能容忍這種傷風敗俗的人或事
We cannot expect god to be on our side
上帝還怎么保佑我們
if we tolerate abominations or those who commit them.
你們倆將被通宵被鎖在這里
You two will remain in the stocks overnight.
而你小子  將一生背負
And you, boy, will bear the mark of your sins
你罪孽的印記
the rest of your life.
不要啊  求你了
No, please. Please!
行行好吧  西布里
For god's sakes, Sibley.
當眾羞辱和鞭刑已經夠他受的了
The stocks and the lashings are punishment enough.
不要啊
No!
私通者
Fornicator!
"你們不要論斷人
Judge not...
免得你們被論斷"
lest ye be judged.
出自圣經《馬太福音》第七章7:1
誰在說話
Who said that?
這是耶穌說的  你也許聽說過他
Jesus. You might have heard of him.
約翰·奧登
John Alden.
別以為有我對你父親的那點尊重
My respect for your father's memory
你就可以在這里肆無忌憚
can only shield you so long.
你今晚就要出征了  別在這惹事
It's a good thing you're mustering out tonight.
不管你愿不愿意  西布里現在手握重權
Like it or not, Sibley's in charge.
他或許能容忍你父親
He tolerated your father,
但他可不會容你在這放肆
but he won't be happy till he sees you swing.
你今天還沒學到教訓嗎
Didn't you learn anything today?
是啊  是啊  如果多給我一個晚上的時間
Yes, yes, if I have to spend one more night
接近喬治·西布里那個王八蛋
under the same stars as that bastard George Sibley,
我會像殺豬樣宰了他
I will gut him like the pig that he is.
你說這話會被當眾懲罰的
If -- talking like that will land you in the stocks.
沒機會了
No day soon.
我寧愿死在戰場上
I'd rather die fighting the French and the Indians
也不愿在這被人侮辱
than get pissed on by the good souls of Salem.
所以你是真要走了
So, you're really leaving.
瑪麗  相信我
Mary, trust me.
我會回來找你的
I will come back for you.
看
Look.
這是我僅有的了
This is all that I have.
我以我父母之靈起誓
And I swear on my parents' grave.
這就是我的誓言
This is my vow.
這場戰爭頂多持續一年
This war will not last a year.
前進
Forward!
保持隊形  先生們
Stay in formation, gentlemen.
大概就半天的路程
Isn't but a half-day's ride.
我做不到
I can't make it.
我覺得我又要吐了
I think I'm gonna be sick again.
沒事兒的  進去坐坐就好了
As soon as you sit down inside, it will settle.
讓長者先行  小姑娘
Wait your betters, girl.
愿上帝保佑你
Peace be upon you.
你也是
And upon you.
愿上帝保佑你
Peace be upon you.
你也是
And upon you.
雖然戰爭無情
Though there are things to be said for war.
但對某些人來說  戰死沙場
Gives a certain kind of man someplace to end up
遠比被處以極刑
other than the end of a brand...
更有意義
or a rope.
終有一天你會感謝我的
You'll thank me one day.
堅強點
Stay strong.
今晚之后  一切都將結束
After tonight, it will all be over.
緹圖芭  等等
Tituba, wait.
我改變主意了  我想回去
I've changed my mind. I want to go back.
塞勒姆沒有那孩子的容身之地
There is no place for that child in Salem.
喬治·西布里讓約翰·奧登戰死沙場
George Sibley drove John Alden off to die in the war.
你覺得他要是發現了你懷著約翰的孩子
What do you think he's gonna do to you
他會怎么對你
when he finds out you're pregnant with John's baby?
不要害怕森林
Do not fear the woods.
森林會照顧好那個小小的靈魂的
The woods are gonna take care of that little soul...
還有你
and you.
這是什么地方
What is this place?
你若還想活  就好好躺著
You want to live? Lie still.
求求你
Please.
他留給我的只有這個孩子了
It's all that I have left of him.
別出聲
Hush.
不  等等  我不想這么做
No, wait. I-I-I don't want to do this.
你別無選擇  瑪麗
You don't have a choice, Mary.
求求你
Please.
-這才是你想要的  -拜托
- This is what you want. - Please.
這才是你想要的
This is what you want.
-不  求你了  -讓他進去
- No...please. - Let him in.
不要啊  拜托
No, please.
別過來
Stay there!
約翰  約翰  約翰  救救我
John. John. John, help me.
救我
Help me!
快告訴他
Now tell him.
說吧  說這是你想要的
Say it. This is what you want.
是  是
Yes. Yes!
是我想要的
Yes!
為了彌補你  整個世界都將是你的
All the world shall be yours in return.
整個世界
All the world.
塞勒姆
第一季 第一集
七年后
...來自天堂的熊熊烈火
...from heaven in flaming fire,
將向不信奉上帝之人尋仇
taking vengeance upon all those who know not God,
向違背教義之人尋仇  自己來看清真理吧
who have disobeyed the gospel! Read for yourself the truth.
可怕的真理
The terrible truth --
黑色安息日
我們中有巫師  塞勒姆有惡魔
Witches among us, the devil in Salem.
給您  先生
For you, sir.
不用
No.
塞勒姆教堂
上帝賜予我們力量
慢點  慢點
Easy. Easy.
這里是奧登家
This is the Alden house,
奧登家的人已經都死光了
and there ain't any Aldens left.
所以你要么是鬼魂  要么就要成為鬼魂了
So you are either a ghost, or you're about to be one.
這樣歡迎別人回家可不是待客之道啊
That's a harsh way to say "Welcome home."
約翰
Johnny?
怎么可能
Can't be.
我聽說你死了啊  戰死了
I heard you was dead -- killed in the war.
我倒是希望死了
I wished I was a couple of times.
好人是不會輕易就死了的
Ah, well, they can't keep a good man down.
我在來的路上看到三個人被絞死示眾
Saw three men strung up on the way into town
公共集會地中間還建了一個新絞刑架
and a new gallows being built in the heart of the common.
這是怎么回事
What the hell is that?
我們的塞勒姆因為巫師的事人心惶惶
Precious Salem caught up in a stinking witch panic.
巫師
Witch panic?
有權有勢的那些人又派誰去平息了
Who did the bigwigs send in to put out the fire,
那個對上帝深信不疑的麥哲嗎
the Almighty increase Mather?
不  是他兒子柯頓
No, his son -- Cotton.
只可惜他比起父親差遠了  就是個廢物
And not a chip off the old block -- barely a splinter.
我記得我們小時候
I remember when we were kids
他就穿得跟個姑娘似的
he used to dress like a girl.
打起架來也扭扭捏捏
Fought like one, too.
他現在長大了
Well, he's all growed-up now.
長成了滿身纏著綾羅綢緞的傻子
A fine fool in fine silk clothes,
但不是普通的傻子  而是最危險的那種
and not just any fool, the most dangerous kind --
自以為無所不知
the kind that thinks he knows everything.
你回來不是為了聽這些屁話的吧
But you didn't come back for all this horseshit.
你回來的目的只有一個
You come back for one thing and one thing only.
說實話  她現在過得很好
Truth told, she's finer than ever.
她是塞勒姆最富有的女人
And she's the richest woman in Salem.
為什么呢
And why not?
因為她現在是西布里的妻子
She's mary Sibley now.
西布里宅
西布里
Sibley?
喬治·西布里
George Sibley.
但他妻子...
But his wife --
幾年前去世了
Died a few years ago.
你離開太長時間了  約翰
You've been gone a long time, John.
時刻做好準備吧
Keep your powder in your bag.
有一天
One day,
你的瑪麗會成為我們國家最富有的寡婦
your Mary will be the richest widow in the country.
司機來了
The driver's at the door
帶來了您的包裹  夫人
with some packages for you, ma'am.
讓他進來
Send him in.
納撒尼爾  帶西布里先生一起走吧
And, Nathaniel, take Mr. Sibley with you.
到洗澡時間了
Time for his bath.
艾薩克  現在告訴我都有哪些新聞吧
Now, Isaac, tell me some news of the world.
今天看到一個人風塵仆仆地進城了
Saw a dusty fella walking into town today.
我簡直不敢相信自己的眼睛
I couldn't believe my eyes.
為什么
Why?
那個人是約翰·奧登
It was John Alden.
歡迎回來  麥哲牧師
Welcome back, Reverend Mather.
朗姆酒   杜松子酒和麥芽酒
Rum, gin, ale?
好
Yes.
我需要三個身強體壯的人
I need three strong men.
我會付錢的
I can pay.
干什么
For what?
去制服一個姑娘
To subdue a girl.
路易絲牧師
Reverend Lewis.
求你幫幫我女兒
Please help my daughter.
注意安全
And be careful.
綁住她
Tie her down!
Tie her down!!
求你了  牧師  求你了  救救我
Please, I beg you, sir. Please, make this stop.
梅西  我也無能為力  除非你告訴我
I can do nothing, Mercy, unless you tell me...
是誰在折磨你
Who is it torments you?
她就在那里
S-she's right there.
她
"She"?
誰在這里
Who is here?
梅西  你必須告訴我
Mercy, you must tell me!
這里還有誰
Who is in this room with us?!
那個女巫  那個老太婆
The hag! The old woman!
她就站在那里
She's standing right there!
求你了
Please.
這是藥
A simple physic.
幫你入睡
To sleep.
求你了  求你了
Please. Please.
我們稱之為魔鬼侵襲...
We call it a spectral attack --
是女巫所為
The work of witches.
為她祈禱吧
Pray for her.
一派胡言
I call bullshit.
她顯然是精神失常了
She's clearly touched in the head.
她需要醫生  不是禱告
She needs a doctor, not your prayers.
別磨蹭  孩子
Don't dawdle, child.
我要你坐到前排
I want you in the front row
柯頓·麥哲定會為你的魅力而傾倒
Where Cotton Mather can't help but be dazzled by your charms.
看在上帝的份上  母親
For heaven's sake, mother,
干脆把我裹進絲綢  放到拍賣會上好了
why not just wrap me in silk and parade me on the auction block?
人類的戰爭不足為懼
Fear no man's war.
只有來自地獄的戰火能摧毀塞勒姆
For only a war from hell could destroy Salem.
決不能讓魔鬼
The devil was never going to let
不費一兵一卒
a promised land be built here
就攻占這里
without a fight, without a battle!
巫師所擁有致命的惡意
And witches armed with deadly malice
便是最為狠毒而陰險的武器
are the most malignant and insidious weapons
在這場戰役
in that battle,
這場戰爭中
in that war.
只要塞勒姆有一個巫師  便足以毀滅
Even a single witch in Salem is enough to destroy
我們所建立的一切  和我們所有的遠大愿景
everything we have built and ever hope to build here!
如今  我們已經處決了三名巫師
Now, we have already killed three of them,
但他們的惡意仍未消逝
and yet their malice continues unabated.
為什么
Why?
因為我們之中仍有巫師存在
Because there are still witches here among us!
或許就在這座大廳里
Perhaps in this very hall!
設想這些在暗處的敵人  擁有未知的武器和巫術
Imagine a foe you can't see armed with weapons unknown
看上去卻和常人別無二致
and the ability to appear as any one of us!
既然如此  你希望誰來指認罪犯
Then how can you hope to identify the correct culprit?
你見過那個女孩了嗎  先生
Have you seen the girl, sir?
即使現在  梅西·路易絲遍體鱗傷
Even now, Mercy Lewis bleeds from 100 wounds --
這些傷絕不會是自殘所致
some impossible to self-inflict.
她將向我們指認犯罪之人
She is the one who will tell us who does this.
我明白了
I see.
重病纏身的可憐女孩  她的瘋言瘋語
The ravings of a poor, sick girl
就能解釋你這說不清的邏輯了嗎
will help you identify what your reason fails to deliver.
我父親
My father --
是  沒錯  你父親
Yes, of course. Your father.
備受大家尊崇的  你的父親
Did your father, whom we all so respect,
讓你代替他過來幫忙的時候
offer you any advice when he sent you in his stead
提供什么建議了嗎
to our aid?
他給出了警告
He...advised caution.
警告
Caution?
因為小麥哲的警告
And are we to take three people hung
我們就要將三人絞死嗎
as the measure of Mather Junior's caution?
在塞勒姆  甚至在全國
There could be nothing worse for Salem,
沒有比巫師追捕行動更可怕的事了
for the country, than a witch hunt.
巫師
Witches.
正是
Indeed.
正如我親愛的丈夫  你們的執行官所言
As my beloved husband, the head of your selectmen, reminds me,
還有比巫師追捕行動更可怕的東西
there is something worse than a witch hunt --
那就是巫師
a witch.
巫師
A witch?
那一定很可怕
Sure, that's bad.
為什么不是食人魔
But why not an ogre...
或是哥布林
or a goblin?
既然要說神話生物  為什么不能是龍
Why not a dragon, long as we're talking about fairy tales?
約翰·奧登
John Alden.
感謝你多年來對我們的英勇守護
We all welcome captain alden home from his long,
歡迎回家  奧登上尉
long service in our defense.
清教徒自知勢力衰減
Puritans know their sun is setting.
沒什么比新的敵人  或者新的老對手
Nothing like a new enemy or a new old enemy
更能籠絡人心了
to get people behind you.
奧登上尉
Captain Alden.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里先生和我明晚會舉辦小型晚宴
Mr. Sibley and I are hosting a small dinner tomorrow night.
你的到來將使舍下蓬蓽生輝
We'd be honored if you'd join.
為什么盯著我
Why are you staring at me?
我甚至不認識你
I don't even know you.
艾薩克
Isaac?
私通者艾薩克
Isaac the fornicator.
藏好你的妻子
Hide your wives.
你的女兒  連羊都得小心點
Hide your daughters. Hell, your sheep!
好吧
All right, look.
你想要我怎么做
So, what do you want from me?
聽我說  約翰·奧登
Listen to me, John Alden.
離開戰場回到塞勒姆
Coming home to Salem to get out of the war
就好比穿越刀山  又跳入火海
is like jumping in the ocean to get out of the rain.
真相秘而不宣
Truth hides.
誰都可能會是他們
They could be anyone.
拜托  他們  他們是誰
Oh, they who? Who's they?
巫師
Witches!
不是神話傳說
Ain't no fairy tale.
巫師是真實存在的
They're real.
這些年來
All these years,
你的瑪麗是唯一向我施以援手的人
your Mary's the only one who's ever done me a good turn.
她不再是我的瑪麗了
She's not my Mary now.
你已經離開過一次了
You left once before.
看看都發生了些什么
Look what happened.
不要再拋下我們了
Don't walk out on us again.
真的有必要如此嗎
Is this really necessary?
巫師的親信
A witches' familiars --
魔鬼  常以動物之形存在
demons, usually in the form of an animal.
貓  鼠  鳥  或者蟾蜍
Cat, rat, a bird, or a toad --
它們只要填飽肚子
they perform all sorts of useful tasks
就能執行各種任務
as long as they're fed.
你也聽到她說的話了
You heard what she told us.
她被迫喂養他們的親信
She was forced to feed their familiars.
因此她身上一定有標志
She must be searched for the marks --
那些它們用以吮吸的裂口
teats where she suckled them.
請幫幫她
Please help her.
"可是地與海的居民有禍了
"Woe to the inhabitants of the earth and of the sea!
因為魔鬼知道自己的時日無多
"For the devil has come down unto you with great wrath
就懷著烈怒下到你們那里去了"
because he knoweth that he hath but a short time."
《啟示錄》12章12節
Revelations chapter 12:12.
看得出世界末日
I see the end of the world
讓你更賣力了
urges you onto greater efforts.
它敦促著我們每個人
Mm, as it must us all.
我的祖母以前總喜歡
Our granny used to scare us silly
用女巫的故事嚇唬我們
with those witch stories.
不過她真的嚇到我兄弟們了
But she'd really terrify my brothers.
她說女巫能偷走男人的
She told them witches could steal a man's --
你喜歡這樣嗎  格里安娜
Would you like that, Gloriana,
不必受到任何男人的束縛
without the bother of the man attached?
你不同
Not this man.
親愛的
My darling.
下次見  長官
See you next time, governor.
我只是來關照窮苦人民
Just attending to the poor.
毫無疑問  精神匱乏的窮人
No doubt -- and the poor in spirit.
奧登上尉是嗎
Captain alden, right?
孩提之后我就沒有見過你
I haven't seen you since we were children.
本來期待能在哈佛見到你
I expected to see you up at Harvard.
沒想到你卻加入了民兵團
Surprised to hear that you'd run off to join the militia --
像那些仆人一樣
like a servant.
我很樂意花上四年
I would have loved to spend four years
去數數針頭上有多少天使  不過
counting angels on the heads of pins, but...
戰爭當前
...there was a war on.
真是可惜
Pity.
學習讓我受益匪淺
I owe everything to my education.
學校教你怎么追捕巫師了嗎
Taught you everything about hunting witches?
沒有
No.
不過我父親在艾塞克斯時便對此頗有研究
But my father burnt scores back in Essex,
而且我讀過與之相關的一切書籍
and I've read every book there is on the subject --
八種語言的
in eight languages.
那你就是從書上學會怎么捉巫師了
So, you learned your hunting from books.
就像是從你未經世事的小姨那里
Well, that's a bit like learning the facts of life
學習生活真相
from your maiden aunt.
但也無所謂了
But never mind.
你剛好在這
You're here now,
又是巫師專家
and you're the expert on witches,
讓我問問你
So let me ask you.
那些可怕的巫師想要什么
What do these awful witches want, huh?
與我們渴望的一樣
The same thing we all want...
一個屬于自己的國家
...a country of their own.
我卻在這浪費時間攻打區區印第安人
And here I've been wasting my time fighting mere Indians.
晚安  高材生
Good night, Harvard.
喂食時間到了
Time for your feeding.
很好
Yes.
來人啊  幫幫我
Someone, help me!
救命
Help me.
很好
Yes.
不要
No.
救我 救我
Help me! Help!
救命
Help!
喬治  別掙扎
George, don't fight it.
那只會讓你更痛苦
You know it only hurts more.
你奪走了我的一切  喬治·西布里
You took away everything I had, George Sibley...
我深愛的一切
everything I loved.
你知道這種感覺多美妙嗎
Can you imagine how good it feels
奪走你的所有
to take everything you have,
摧毀你建立的一切
destroy all you've built,
并親手毀滅你的靈魂
and devour your very soul?
好了
All done.
我想敬我們的女主人
I would like to make a toast to our hostess,
瑪麗·西布里
Mary sibley,
她向我們展示了真正的虔誠和美麗
who has shown us that true piety and true beauty
同樣值得贊頌
amount to the same worship.
沒錯
Indeed.
美麗是丑陋墮落的世界上
Beauty is the last miracle allowed in an ugly...
最后一個奇跡
fallen world.
霍爾法官和我
Magistrate Hale and I are concerned
為我們女兒的內在美而擔憂  麥哲牧師
about our daughter's inner beauty, Reverend Mather.
或許你可以為她推薦一個導師
Perhaps you could suggest a tutor for her,
一個哈佛畢業生  向您本人這樣的
a Harvard man -- like yourself?
我覺得書上能學到的東西有限
I believe there is only so much you can learn from books.
經驗才是真正的老師
Experience is our true teacher.
你同意嗎  奧登上尉
Don't you agree, captain Alden?
這取決于那些經驗是什么了
Well, that depends on the experience.
你的經驗一定非常吸引人  那些印第安人
Yours must have been fascinating -- with the indians.
他們如此神秘
They're so mysterious,
如此接近自然
So...natural.
自然
Natural?
要我說是反常
"Unnatural," I'd say.
沒有靈魂的野蠻人
Soulless savages.
相信我  夫人  印第安人有靈魂
I assure you, ma'am, the indians do have souls,
如果我們有的話
if any of us do.
"如果"
"If"?
那巫師呢
And what about witches?
他們也有靈魂嗎
Do they have souls, too?
他們有
They do.
但他們將自己的靈魂出賣給了魔鬼
But they have deeded them to the devil himself
以換取權力和他們渴望的一切事物
in exchange for powers and all that they desire.
-魔鬼協議嗎  -沒錯
- A contract? - Indeed.
真是諷刺
Ironic.
我相信在法律中
As I believe, by law,
女性只有通過丈夫
a woman's not allowed to enter a contract
才能與別人簽訂合同
but through the agency of their husband.
納撒尼爾
Nathaniel.
好的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
并不是所有的巫師都是女巫
Not all witches are women.
你認為呢  奧登上尉
And what do you think, captain Alden?
我不知道
I don't know.
我認為有些事情還是得眼見為實
I think some things just beggar belief,
就像是誠實的法國人  或是忠誠的女人
like an honest frenchman or a faithful woman,
這些我只有親眼見到了才會相信
things that I'll believe in if and when I see one.
我發現比起巫師
I find I worry more
我還是更擔心法國人和
about the french and the indian attacks
印第安人的入侵
than I do witches.
你怎么看  奧登上尉
What's your opinion, captain Alden?
我們的防守如何
Just how vulnerable are we?
你還好嗎  奧登上尉
Are you all right, captain Alden?
可能這些豐盛的食物我還是不太習慣
I think this rich food doesn't agree with me.
呼吸一下新鮮空氣或許能有所幫助
Some fresh air might help.
有人跟我說你死了
I was told you were killed.
那是在你嫁給西布里之前還是之后
Was that before or after you married Sibley?
我記得有人對我說過
I remember being told once
戰爭不會超過一年
that the war wouldn't last a year.
這不是我能決定的
That wasn't up to me.
我一直在等著你
I waited for you.
年復一年  你卻杳無音訊
Years and years without a word.
我沒法寫信
I couldn't write.
當然了
No, of course not.
忙于拯救國家
Too busy saving the country.
不是的
Not exactly.
我被俘虜了
I was captured.
他們的神父對其他人說不要奪走這個
Their priest man told the others not to take this away from me.
他說宇宙由誓言所構成
He said the universe itself was made out of vows,
破壞誓言會帶來嚴重后果
and breaking them carries consequences.
我知道這只是半枚銀幣
I know that this is just half a silver coin,
如今  你的金銀珠寶享之不盡
and you have... no shortage of silver now.
瑪麗  跟我走吧
Mary, come with me.
現在  今晚
Now...tonight.
我在紐約的銀行有一些積蓄
I have money in a bank in new york.
那里很不一樣
It's different there.
你不會見到一個清教徒
There's not a puritan in sight.
現在還來得及
It's not too late.
我們能在一起
We can be together
無論何地
anywhere.
除了這里
Anywhere but here.
紐約
New York?
對
Yeah.
那是在你被俘虜之前還是之后
Is that before or after you were captured?
那個晚上你離開了這里
You walk out of here one night,
這么多年后你才回來
and you come back years later.
你以為我...
A-and you think that --
瑪麗
Mary.
過來
Come here.
不
No.
我不能
I can't.
不可能了
It's impossible.
他不會允許
He'd never let me.
西布里夫人
Now, now, Mrs. Sibley.
就算是您也不能獨占咱們的貴客
Even you have no right to monopolize a guest
我們的奧登上尉
as fascinating as Captain Alden,
我可是有珍貴的禮物要送你
for whom I have a rare gift,
咱們來點圭亞那的雪茄和白蘭地如何
a cigar of tobacco from Guyana with some Brandy.
恐怕這一切
I'm afraid all this...
文明的吃飯喝酒的方式讓我不適  長官
civilized eating and drinking has laid me out, magistrate.
你告訴我他死了
You told me he was dead!
預言從不會如此精確  親愛的
It's not like counting sheep, honey.
總會有模糊的盲點
more like counting shadows.
但這都無關緊要
But it don't change a thing.
約翰·奧登比起你眼前的一切算得了什么
What's John Alden compared to all that lies before you?
別哭了  女人
Stop your weeping, woman.
那個人不配得到你的眼淚
That boy don't deserve those tears.
不是為他而流
They're not for him.
是為了我曾經的少女心
They're for the girl I once was.
你早已回不去了
That girl belongs to somebody else now.
是他把你留給了一群狼嗎
Was it he that left you to the wolves?
不是的  孩子
No, child.
是他從狼群中把你救出
It was he that saved you from the wolves
造就成今日的你
and raised you up to all of this.
你有更偉大的目標
You have a grand vision.
不要忘記
Don't lose sight of it.
明天  月亮將與我們同在
Tomorrow, the moon is with us.
明天  序幕拉開
Tomorrow, it begins.
將你所有的憤怒和痛苦交給卡耐馬惡鬼吞噬
Leave your anger and your pain for the kenaima to feed on.
他違背過自己的誓言嗎
Has he not been true to his vow?
如今  你的敵人都已成為你的奴隸
Are not your enemies now your slaves?
難道你不是擁有了渴望的一切
Do you not have everything that you desire --
財富  權力
Wealth, power?
幾乎一切
Almost everything.
抱歉  夫人  有人求見
Pardon me, ma'am. A gentleman to see you.
科里先生
Mr. Corey.
閣下有何貴干
To what do I owe the pleasure?
我在想是不是應該和你談談  夫人
I was wondering if I might talk to you, ma'am.
我有過一個小農場
I had a small farm.
它先是傷了我的心
First, it broke my heart.
然后傷了我的后背
then it broke my back.
你我都知道  心會痊愈
As you and I both know, the heart heals.
背傷卻永遠不會
The back never does.
從此我開始靠設陷阱捕獵為生
I took up trapping.
這種拮據的生活當初毀了印第安人
It's a meager living -- ruined the Indians.
現在正在逐漸毀掉我
Now it's ruining me.
設陷阱的時候  獵物通常都在夜里踏入陷阱
Thing about trapping is you get your good catch at night.
可到了早上  卻通常成了別人的食物
But by morning, it's someone else's meal.
至于我  我會守著我的陷阱
Me, I stay with my traps.
很精彩  科里先生  但是
Fascinating, Mr. Corey, but --
這就是為什么我來到這
That's why I was there...
我知道那天晚上
The night you did it...
你和你的仆人都干了些什么
You and your cinnamon girl.
你等了很久才來找我啊
You waited a long time.
因為之前不涉及到任何人
Nobody's business till now.
但那個被你燒掉的孩子是約翰·奧登的
But that was John Alden's baby that you buried out there.
他為你如此著迷  他有權知道真相
And the way he feels about you, he has a right to know.
所以該由你來說呢
So, are you gonna tell him?
還是我來
Or am I?
該死的
Oh, blast this wretched thing.
畫得很不錯
That's not bad.
路易斯牧師說繪畫是邪神崇拜
Reverend Lewis says drawing is idolatry,
如同崇拜自然或者什么
like worshiping nature or something.
總比崇拜些更糟糕的東西好
Well, there might be worse things to worship.
有機會的話  我想為你畫像
I'd like to draw you sometime.
我可不確定是否想看到畫中的自己
I'm not sure I'd like to see a portrait of me.
再說了  我也沒有時間
Besides, I have no time to sit.
我要離開了
I'm on way out of town.
這么快
So soon?
是因為害怕巫師嗎
Afraid of witches...
還是怕被當成是巫師
or being taken for one?
紐約離這可有一段路程
It's a long way to New York.
祝你有愉快的一天
Good day.
我不是故意嚇你的
Oh, I didn't mean to frighten you.
我沒被嚇到
Oh, I'm not frightened.
只是感到意外
Just surprised.
那是當然
Yes, of course --
對一個敢獨自在墓地里素描的女孩這算什么
A girl brave enough to sketch in a graveyard.
我不害怕死人
I'm not afraid of the dead,
活人也不怕
nor the living for that matter.
那是因為你對死亡一無所知
That's because you know nothing of death
對生命更加的無知
And less of life.
我可以教給你
I could teach you --
關于生命
about life...
和死亡
and death...
還有二者之間的東西
and many things in between.
你知道幾乎每個埋在這的女人都死于什么
Do you know what killed nearly every woman buried here?
愛情
Love.
大多數都死于分娩
Most died in childbirth.
所以說愛情之于女人就好比戰爭之于男人
So, love is to a woman what war is to a man --
都是所能做的最致命的事情
the most deadly thing they'll do.
只有傻子才會迫不及待的奔向戰爭和愛情
Only a fool runs quickly to war or love.
你自己小心為妙
You'd best watch yourself.
謝謝您  西布里夫人
Thank you...Mrs. Sibley.
對于您的智慧我真是望塵莫及
I can only aspire to your happy wisdom.
巫師們在哪里見面
Where do the witches meet?
樹林里
In the woods.
有多少人
How many?
我不知道
I don't know.
他們是誰
Who are they?
我
I --
我看不到他她們的臉
I can't see their faces.
好像是一些動物的頭顱
Like there's these heads of animals
一頭牡鹿  一頭豬和一只狼
like a stag and a pig and a wolf.
可你還是知道他們是誰
But you know who they are?
是的
Yes.
他們的名字
Their names.
為什么你不告訴我他們的名字
Why won't you tell me their names?
她不允許我
She won't let me.
她
"She"?
-是的  -誰
- Yes. - Who?
她是誰
Who is she?
告訴我
Tell me.
-我不能  -把名字告訴我
- I can't. - Tell me the names!
天哪  梅西
My god, Mercy.
盡管她不能說出名字
Though she cannot speak a name,
她會指出女巫是誰
she will show us the witch.
天吶  不要
Oh, no!
抱歉  上尉
Sorry, Captain.
你現在不能離開塞勒姆
You can't leave Salem just yet.
有些東西你得看看
Something you've got to see.
是他嗎  那個巫師
Is this him, the witch?
我想是吧
I think so.
所有的書籍上都說如果受害者
All the books say if the victim --
別管的你書怎么說
Never mind your books.
他是不是巫師
Is this the witch?
他不愿開口  既不承認也不否認
He won't plead either way.
這樣嗎
Is that so?
本來也不是什么真正的指控
Won't dignify the accusation.
一個小女孩朝著你吐口水
If you can call a young girl's
這也能算是指控嗎
spit an accusation.
要我開口的話
What I have to say,
我要跟約翰·奧登上尉談
I'll say to Captain John Alden.
只要你把奧登上尉找來
You just find me Captain Alden.
我可是有不少話要講呢
I'll have plenty to say.
我已經派人找過奧登上尉
I have sent men for captain Alden,
但是我被告知他已經離開了
but I'm told he's left town.
想辦法讓他招供
Just obtain a plea.
如果他還是不肯說呢
And if he remains silent?
大家賦予了你權力
You've been granted power.
好好利用它  從他嘴里逼出答案
Use it. Press him for an answer.
看看令他守口如瓶的惡魔是否
Let the same devil that holds his tongue
經得起巨石的碾壓
hold the stones.
快點  集會馬上就要開始了
Hurry. The sabbath is about to begin.
一  二  三 四
One, two, three, and four.
魔鬼  聽吾之召喚
Raise the devil to our door.
眾生之靈  豬  狼  羊
Call the pig, the wolf, the ram.
應吾之召  眾靈重現
Come to the circle, all who can.
他將再次行走于這片土地
Make him walk on floor to roof.
我們將與他舉杯共飲
Drink to him with horn and hoof.
一  二  三  四
One, two, three, and four.
魔鬼已至
The devil is here.
別再沉睡
Now sleep no more.
世間萬物將盡在你掌握
And all the world shall be yours in return.
如果你說的巫師們在這集會
If your witches meet here,
那他們夜視一定不錯
they got better night eyes than I do.
他們根本不需要視力
They don't need night eyes.
夜晚就是他們的眼睛
The night is their eyes.
這都是什么鬼東西
What the hell is this?
給惡魔的獻祭
Gifts to the devil himself --
都是未出生的嬰兒
The unborn.
無辜者之血
Cruor innocentia.
巫師  瘟疫
Maleficarum. Pestilentia.
五朔節之夜
Walpurgisnacht.
根據德國神話  四月三十日夜晚女巫將與惡魔一起狂歡
儀式已完成
Consummatum est.
一切即將開始
Now it begins.
祭祀圈被破壞了
The circle was broken.
被誰
By who?
撒旦
Satan!
我請求你  先生
Please, sir.
我也不愿這么做
I don't want to to do this.
那就別這么做
Then don't.
講講道理吧
Be reasonable, man.
我有合法的權力對你進行逼供
I have the power to press you for an answer.
只要你開口  承認自己有罪
All you have to do is say the words "Guilty"
或是無罪
or "Not guilty,"
我們就能停止這一切
And we can stop all of this.
如果我承認有罪  黎明之前我就會被絞死
If I say "Guilty," you'll hang me before dawn.
如果我堅持自己無罪
And if I say not,
我的命運仍將握在你們這群混蛋手中
my fate is still in the hands of you bastards.
所以我寧愿沉默  將命運交給上帝
I'll hold my peace and trust in the Lord.
把石頭放下來
Lower the stones!
我再問你一次
I ask you again.
你承認自己有罪
Are you guilty...
或是無罪
or not?
我們死定了
We're dead.
不會的
No, we are not.
離死期也不遠了
Good as.
這一切你不是早就見識過嗎
I thought you've seen them before.
你想讓我看到這些  我也確實看到了
You wanted me to see them, and I saw them.
可他們也看見了我們
And they saw us.
我跟你說過  他們可能是任何人
And I told you they could be anybody.
好吧
Okay, just...
冷靜點
calm down.
你有什么話要說嗎
Have you something to say?
再加點石頭吧
More stones.
吉爾斯
Giles!
都給我離他遠點
Get the hell off of him!
奧登
Alden!
他死了
He's dead!
"地與海的居民
"Woe to the inhabitants...
你們有禍了
"of the earth and of the sea.
因為魔鬼即將降臨"
For the devil has come down unto you."
出自圣經《啟示錄》12:12
你這個狗娘養的
Son of a bitch. Son of a...
不
No! No!
放手
Get!
我父親是最早踏上塞勒姆這片土地的人
My father's boots were the very first in Salem.
我警告你們這里每一個殺人如麻
And I'm warning every goddamn one of you murdering,
虛假偽善的清教徒混蛋
hypocritical puritan bastards
你們都不會有好下場
that these boots will be the last!
我再問你一次
I will ask you once again.
誰在那里
Who was there?
誰看見了我們
Who saw us?
我也再回答你一次
I will tell you again.
我不知道
I do not know.
當時槍口的火焰太亮了  很難看清
It is difficult to see past a muzzle flash.
那我建議你盡快查清楚  霍爾先生
Then I suggest you find out, Mr. Hale.
現在已經沒法回頭了
There's no turning back.
巫師追捕行動已經開始
The witch hunt has begun,
而主持審判的會是我們
and we will be running the trials.
你明白吧  喬治  不是嗎
You understand that, don't you, George?
你應該最清楚
You best of all.
我們會利用審判
We will use the trials
讓那些清教徒自相殘殺
to turn the puritans against each other.
他們將會追捕  屠殺
They will hunt and kill
最終淹沒于自己的鮮血當中
and drown in their very own blood
直到再無一名清教徒生還
till there's no puritans left standing...
而塞勒姆
And Salem...
將屬于我們
is ours.
塞勒姆